Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 17)
(الحلقة 17)
Back then, you could not protect Xiao Jin Yu.
في ذلك الوقت، لم يكن بإمكانك حماية شياو جين يو.
And now,
والآن،
you cannot protect Lu Zhao either.
أنت أيضًا لا تستطيع حماية لو تشاو.
From beginning to end,
من البداية إلى النهاية،
you have always been my defeated foe!
لقد كنت دائما عدوي المهزوم!
You really think I would not dare to kill you?
هل تعتقد حقا أنني لن أجرؤ على قتلك؟
You would.
انت تريد ذلك.
Of course you would.
بالطبع سوف تفعل ذلك.
You, Xiao Ren, what do you amount to?
أنت، شياو رين، ما الذي تصل إليه؟
Without Xiao Jin Yu to keep you in check,
بدون شياو جين يو لإبقائك تحت السيطرة،
you are nothing but a complete lunatic.
أنت لست سوى مجنون كامل.
There is nothing you cannot do.
لا يوجد شيء لا تستطيع فعله.
It is just that,
إنه فقط ذلك،
if you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
then Lu Zhao...
ثم لو تشاو ...
will also be buried with me.
وسوف يدفن معي أيضًا.
I placed the poison...
وضعت السم...
in the seal paste long ago.
في عجينة الختم منذ زمن طويل.
When she transferred her assets,
عندما نقلت أصولها،
she stamped her fingerprint on the papers, one by one.
لقد ختمت بصمتها على الأوراق، واحدة تلو الأخرى.
The poison had already seeped into her flesh.
لقد تسرب السم بالفعل إلى جسدها.
That is heart-piercing poison.
هذا هو السم الذي يخترق القلب.
The only antidote in this world...
الترياق الوحيد في هذا العالم...
has already been taken by me.
لقد تم أخذها بالفعل من قبلي.
At this point,
عند هذه النقطة،
only if she sleeps with me monthly...
فقط إذا كانت تنام معي شهريًا...
can the poison be suppressed.
هل يمكن قمع السم؟
If you want to save Lu Zhao,
إذا كنت تريد إنقاذ لو تشاو،
you must first get me out of here.
يجب عليك إخراجي من هنا أولاً.
And,
و،
you must personally...
يجب عليك شخصيا...
send her to my bed!
أرسلها إلى سريري!
Then,
ثم،
perhaps if I am in a good mood,
ربما إذا كنت في مزاج جيد،
I can be merciful and sleep with her.
أستطيع أن أكون رحيمًا وأن أنام معها.
Only then can she barely survive.
حينها فقط يمكنها أن تبقى على قيد الحياة.
Otherwise...
خلاف ذلك...
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
Who am I, Xiao Ren?
من أنا شياو رين؟
Do you not know that better than anyone?
هل أنت لا تعرف ذلك أفضل من أي شخص آخر؟
You just wait for your death.
انتظر موتك فقط .
I, Xiao Ren,
أنا، شياو رن،
will save my woman myself.
سأنقذ امرأتي بنفسي.
Half of the fiends in the Hall of Yama...
نصف الشياطين في قاعة ياما...
were sent there by me.
لقد تم إرسالهم إلى هناك من قبلي.
After you go down,
بعد النزول،
you will not be lonely.
لن تكون وحيدا.
Xiao Ren!
شياو رن!
Today is the last day.
اليوم هو اليوم الأخير.
If we do not find the antidote soon, I am afraid...
إذا لم نجد الترياق قريبا، أخشى...
Master.
يتقن.
Ice-Soul Blade?
شفرة الروح الجليدية؟
The Ice-Soul Blade can only be obtained in the Northern Frontier.
لا يمكن الحصول على شفرة الروح الجليدية إلا في الحدود الشمالية.
The Northern Frontier is so far away.
الحدود الشمالية بعيدة جدًا.
How did you get it so fast?
كيف حصلت عليه بهذه السرعة؟
Only the Ice-Soul Blade...
فقط شفرة الروح الجليدية...
can remove the Golden Silkworm intact.
يمكن إزالة دودة القز الذهبية سليمة.
When used as medicine, the Golden Silkworm...
عند استخدامه كدواء، فإن دودة القز الذهبية...
can neutralize all poisons.
يمكنه تحييد جميع السموم.
But once it is ground into medicine,
ولكن بمجرد أن يتم طحنه وتحويله إلى دواء،
apart from curing poison, it has no other effect.
ليس له أي تأثير آخر سوى علاج السم .
The one within your body has been there so long...
إن الذي في جسدك كان هناك لفترة طويلة...
that it has already fused with your heart.
أنها اندمجت بالفعل مع قلبك.
If we were to take it out, you would be in excruciating pain.
إذا أخرجناها، سوف تشعر بألم شديد.
Once the Golden Silkworm leaves your body,
بمجرد أن تترك دودة القز الذهبية جسدك،
you will lose the constitution...
سوف تفقد الدستور...
that resists all poisons and feels no pain.
الذي يقاوم كل السموم ولا يشعر بالألم.
I have even experienced the pain of losing her.
لقد عشت حتى الألم الناتج عن فقدانها.
What can be more painful than that day?
هل هناك يوم أكثر إيلاما من ذلك اليوم؟
This Golden Silkworm...
هذه الدودة القز الذهبية...
was given to me by her.
لقد أعطتني إياها.
Now, I am just returning it to its owner.
الآن، أنا فقط أعيده إلى صاحبه.
Do it.
افعلها.
I will do it myself.
سأفعل ذلك بنفسي.
Hurry.
عجل.
Administer the medicine as soon as possible.
إعطاء الدواء في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Yes, I understand.
نعم، أفهم ذلك.
Do not be afraid.
لا تخف.
You will wake up soon.
سوف تستيقظ قريبا.
I will not let anything happen to you.
لن أسمح بحدوث أي شيء لك.
By the Emperor's order,
بأمر الإمبراطور،
the Prince of Chu, Situ Xian,
أمير تشو، سيتو شيان،
colluded with foreign tribes,
تواطأ مع القبائل الأجنبية،
plotted treason,
خيانة مدبرة
and has gravely betrayed His Majesty's grace.
وقد خان نعمة جلالته بشكل خطير.
He is hereby stripped of his princely title,
وقد تم تجريده بموجب هذا من لقبه الأميري،
reduced to a commoner,
تم تقليصها إلى عامة الناس،
paraded before the people for three days,
تم عرضه أمام الشعب لمدة ثلاثة أيام،
and confined for life.
ومحتجزًا مدى الحياة.
His concubine Liu...
محظيته ليو...
is given safflower...
يعطى القرطم...
and sent to the Bureau of Entertainment.
وأرسلت إلى مكتب الترفيه.
- Kill him! - It is all your fault.
- اقتله! - كل هذا خطؤك.
Situ Xian!
الموقع شيان!
- Kill him! - You forced my wife to her death!
- اقتلوه! - لقد أجبرت زوجتي على الموت!
You harmed my son!
لقد أذيت ابني!
- You animal! - I will fight you to the death!
- يا حيوان! - سأقاتلك حتى الموت!
He was castrated!
لقد تم خصيه!
You had it coming!
لقد كان يستحق ذلك!
You got what you deserved!
لقد حصلت على ما تستحقه!
Serves you right!
لقد خدمك بشكل صحيح!
- You castrated cripple! - You got what you deserved!
- أيها المقعد المخصي! - لقد حصلت على ما تستحقه!
The heavens see our plight!
السماء ترى محنتنا!
You animal!
يا حيوان!
You had it coming!
لقد كان يستحق ذلك!
Serves you right!
لقد خدمك بشكل صحيح!
- Well done! - You had it coming!
- أحسنت! - لقد كان يستحق ذلك!
You have no conscience!
ليس لديك ضمير!
You got what you deserved!
لقد حصلت على ما تستحقه!
Kill him!
اقتله!
Die!
ال!
You are not human!
أنت لست إنسانًا!
Before the annex was raided,
قبل أن تتم مداهمة الملحق،
I had already moved all the weapons.
لقد نقلت جميع الأسلحة بالفعل.
Please do not worry.
من فضلك لا تقلق.
Very good.
جيد جدًا.
Your mission is complete.
مهمتك تمت.
Our great cause is nearly complete.
قضيتنا العظيمة اكتملت تقريبا.
Only one step remains.
لم يتبقى سوى خطوة واحدة.
Do you mean...
هل تقصد...
the Imperial Palace Defense Map?
خريطة دفاع القصر الإمبراطوري؟
But only the Xuntian Sect leader...
ولكن فقط زعيم طائفة شونتيان...
is qualified to keep this map.
مؤهل للاحتفاظ بهذه الخريطة.
Xiao Jin Yu died so suddenly...
لقد مات شياو جين يو فجأة...
that she had no time to hand it over to Xiao Ren.
أنها لم يكن لديها الوقت لتسليمها إلى شياو رين.
And ever since Xiao Jin Yu died,
ومنذ أن مات شياو جين يو،
Xiao Ren has been entangled with Lu Zhao.
لقد تورط شياو رين مع لو تشاو.
He never looked for the Map.
لم يبحث عن الخريطة أبدًا.
Xiao Ren has always only had eyes for Xiao Jin Yu.
لقد كانت عيون شياو رين دائمًا موجهة نحو شياو جين يو فقط.
How could he suddenly become so devoted to Lu Zhao?
كيف يمكنه فجأة أن يصبح مخلصًا جدًا للو تشاو؟
I have always found it very strange.
لقد وجدته دائمًا غريبًا جدًا.
Ever since she woke up from the fall at the birthday banquet,
منذ أن استيقظت من السقوط في حفل عيد الميلاد،
her personality has changed drastically.
لقد تغيرت شخصيتها بشكل جذري.
It is as if she is a different person.
كأنها شخص مختلف.
Miss, you are finally awake.
آنسة، لقد استيقظت أخيرا.
Master.
يتقن.
You are awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
What is wrong with me?
ما هي مشكلتي ؟
Why did you sleep here?
لماذا نمت هنا؟
It is all because of that animal, Situ Xian.
كل هذا بفضل هذا الحيوان، سيتو شيان.
Master had to...
كان على المعلم أن...
Situ Xian poisoned you.
لقد سممك سيتو شيان.
I had to find the antidote for you...
لقد كان علي أن أجد لك الترياق...
and investigate the Prince of Chu's case.
والتحقيق في قضية أمير تشو.
I was too tired.
لقد كنت متعبًا جدًا.
So I slept with you for a while.
لقد نمت معك لفترة من الوقت.
How was my poison cured?
كيف تم علاج السم الخاص بي؟
Do you not trust my methods?
هل لا تثق بطرقي؟
What is so hard about getting the antidote...
ما هو الصعب في الحصول على الترياق...
from a pampered prince?
من أمير مدلل؟
Are you hurt?
هل انت مصاب؟
No.
لا.
Besides,
بجانب،
I have the Golden Silkworm.
لدي دودة القز الذهبية.
Even if I am wounded, I feel no pain.
حتى لو كنت مجروحًا، لا أشعر بألم.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
the Prince of Chu's case has been concluded.
لقد انتهت قضية أمير تشو .
From the Prince of Chu's manor,
من قصر أمير تشو،
we found letters of collusion between him and the Qiang.
لقد عثرنا على رسائل تواطؤ بينه وبين تشيانغ.
We also found the dragon robe...
لقد وجدنا أيضًا رداء التنين ...
and a list of colluding officials.
وقائمة المسؤولين المتواطئين.
His Majesty has decreed...
أصدر جلالته مرسوما...
that he be stripped of his title...
أن يتم تجريده من لقبه...
and confined for life.
ومحتجزًا مدى الحياة.
It is a pity...
إنه لأمر مؤسف...
What is a pity?
ما هي الشفقة؟
It is a pity that your family assets...
من المؤسف أن أصول عائلتك...
were exchanged for weapons by Situ Xian.
تم تبادلها مقابل الأسلحة من قبل Situ Xian.
He stashed them in the annex.
قام بتخزينهم في الملحق.
When we got there,
عندما وصلنا هناك،
Jin Lin was there, setting himself ablaze.
وكان جين لين هناك، يشعل النار في نفسه.
If we could have seized that family fortune,
لو كان بوسعنا الاستيلاء على ثروة تلك العائلة،
we would have had another source...
لقد كان لدينا مصدر آخر...
of military funds to fight the Qiang people.
من الأموال العسكرية لمحاربة شعب تشيانغ.
Let us not talk about this.
دعونا لا نتحدث عن هذا.
I was scared to death.
لقد كنت خائفة حتى الموت.
What is wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I had a nightmare.
لقد كان عندي كابوس.
In the dream, you were surrounded...
في الحلم كنت محاطًا بـ...
by many people trying to kill you.
من قبل العديد من الأشخاص الذين يحاولون قتلك.
I should have been there by your side.
كان ينبغي أن أكون بجانبك.
Right there with you.
أنا معك هناك.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
It is just a dream.
إنه مجرد حلم.
Look.
ينظر.
You have protected me well.
لقد حميتني جيدا.
You did not lose me.
لم تخسرني.
And you will not lose me.
ولن تخسرني .
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
there will be no more...
لن يكون هناك المزيد...
barriers between us.
الحواجز بيننا.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
Are you sure about this?
هل أنت متأكد من هذا؟
In my life, I have never known regret.
في حياتي لم أعرف الندم أبدًا.